José Martins

Email: josepedromartins.dev@gmail.com, Phone: +351 969-559-096, Portfolio: josepedro-martins.github.io

SUMMARY

I am a Gameplay Programmer and Front-End Web Developer, with very good skills in C#, C++, HTML, CSS and WordPress. I have practice working with Unreal Engine and Unity, having developed single and multiplayer projects, and creating engaging experiences in games.

Accustomed to working with close deadlines and team-based environment, having to manage and assist with project organization.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Proficiency using C#, C++, and other OOP languages.
- Experienced working with WordPress, HTML and CSS.
- 3+ Years of working with video games.
- 4+ Years of working with web development.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer Intern, Fullback | Sports Tech & Sports Management Consulting

November 2019 - May 2020

- Constructed the main architecture and design for the website.
- Built and coded the layout for each page, with WordPress and CSS.
- Received ratings of excellent for every performance and task I have developed.

Full Stack Developer Intern, CodeBehind Portugal

Dates June 2018 - August 2018

- Programmed both back-end and front-end content for their clients.
- Fixed a ticket support system.

Game Programmer, Freelance

Dates September 2020 – Present

- Developed different genres of video games, using Unreal Engine and Unity.
- Accustomed to team work and task management.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN GAMES AND MULTIMEDIA – INSTITUTO POLITÉCNICO DE LEIRIA – PORTUGAL

- Particularized in programming with C# and C++.
- Knowledgeable of Multiplayer, Networking and Artificial Intelligence.

•